bigbangclick.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy - BigBangClick SEM Bid Management

## Last updated: August 8th, 2011

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that BigBangClick ("Service Provider", "we" or "our") treats the information you provide while using BigBangClick.com ("Website"). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page, so check back often. Continued access of the Website by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

## The Type of Information the Website Collects

The Website generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Optional information such as your age or gender may also be requested.

Our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university.

BigBangClick also serves as an agent our clients, in that we provide our services for the benefit of the client. Each client instructs us as to what types of data it would like us to collect on its behalf. This data may include search engine referral, purchase behavior and related information. We use persistent cookies and tracking pixels to determine activity at the client's site.

We may further collect technical information about client’s websites for technical reasons and in order to improve our services.

## How We Uses Information Provided by You

Service Provider uses your user name and password to grant you access to and use of the Website. Your e-mail address will be used, at your request, to send you a copy of your user name and password. If you provide personally identifiable information, it will be used to provide you with the service you have requested. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

We also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if you choose to purchase items through features on the Website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card processing and order fulfillment. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the site that may be managed or participated in by third parties, such as auction services or shopping areas. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third party(ies), each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While Service Provider will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, Service Provider does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. We may also provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, search warrants, court orders, or other legal process.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website.

While your personally identifying information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by Service Provider, its parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information from and/or about our Website users may be among the transferred assets.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. BigBangClick uses cookies to enhance the user experience of our web site by means such as storing password or user preference information. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site with the only drawback being the disablement of some of the usability features of our site. Some of our business partners may use cookies on their site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. BigBangClick also uses cookies to track and monitor usage of the website by users for the purposes of marketing and website improvement. The data collected from these cookies will never be shared with an external source and will be used for internal purposes only.

## Information Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures in order to protect and safeguard the personal information we collect online. We limit access to your personal information only to employees who need to have access to such information in order to provide you all the activities related to the Site and services.

Because no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure, and no system of physical or electronic security is impenetrable, Service Provider can not guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Website.
